David M. Stowe Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Resource Files: ABCFM/UCBWM Documents, 1806-1996; Series V
  - Missionary Circular Letters
    - China; India, 1921, 1931, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
    - China; Greece; Mexico; Africa; France; Greece; Philippines; Angola; India; Japan, 1940-1949 (Box 35, Folder 4-30)
    - Korea; Mexico; Philippines; Africa; China; France; India; Angola; Greece; Japan; Turkey; France'; Hong Kong; Indonesia; Austria; Round-up Letters (Letter of the Month), 1949-1956 (Box 36, Folder 31-71)
    - Micronesia; Philippines; Southern Rhodesia; Turkey; Africa; Angola; China; India; Japan; Round-up Letters, 1956-1959 (Box 37, Folder 72-100)
    - Africa; Angola; China; Ghana; Greece; India; Indonesia; Japan; Philippines; South Africa; Southern Rhodesia; Trust Territory of the Pacific; Turkey; Round-up Letters, 1959-1962 (Box 38, Folder 101-129)
    - Angola; Central America; Ceylon; Eastern Caroline Islands; Ghana; Greece; Hong Kong; India; Indonesia; Japan; Lebanon; Philippines; South Africa; Southern Rhodesia; Taiwan; Togo; Trust Territory of the Pacific; Turkey; Angola; Central America; Children's Letters; Best Letters; Round-up Letters, 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 130-159)
    - Angola; Central America (Mexico, Honduras, Costa Rica, Ecuador); China; Ghana; India; Indonesia; Japan; Lebanon; Malawi; Philippines; South Africa; Southern Rhodesia; Syria; Tanzania; Turkey; Round-up Letters, 1963-1967 (Box 40, Folder 160-192)
    - Angola; Argentina; Australia; Botswana; Brazil; Central America; China; Cyprus; Ecuador; Ghana; India; Indonesia; Japan; Near East; Philippines; South Africa; Southern Rhodesia; Togo; Turkey; Trust Territory of the Pacific; Zaire; Zambia; Children's Letters; Round-up Letters, 1967-1974 (Box 41, Folder 193-244)
    - Africa; Angola; Argentina; Asia; Australia; Bangladesh; Botswana; Cameroon; Central America; Cyprus; France; Germany; Ghana; Guatemala; India; Indonesia; Japan; Lebanon; Mexico; Middle East; Mozambique; Philippines; Sierra Leone; South Africa; South Korea; Southern Rhodesia; Switzerland; Tanzania; Togo; Turkey; Zaire; Zambia, 1974-1978 (Box 42, Folder 245-313)
    - Africa; Asia; Australia; Botswana; Cameroon; Central America; China; Germany; Ghana; India; Indonesia; Jamaica; Japan; Kenya; Lebanon; Marshall Islands; Pacific Region; Pakistan; Philippines; South Africa; South America (Nicaragua, Peru); Sri Lanka; Swaziland; Taiwan; Tanzania; Togo; Turkey; Zambia; Children's Letters, 1979-1983 (Box 43, Folder 314-360)
    - Africa; China; East Asia; England; Europe; India; Indonesia; Jamaica; Japan; Latin America; Lebanon; Marshall Islands; Middle East; Philippines; Somalia; South Africa; Southern Asia; Sri Lanka; Taiwan; Turkey; Zambia; Zimbabwe, 1983-1987 (Box 44, Folder 361-406)
    - Turkey, 1984 (Box 178, Folder 27)
    - Africa; East Asia; China; Japan; Latin America; Southern Asia; Turkey, 1988-1998, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 407-416)
  - Board reports and meetings
    - ABCFM Almanac of Missions, 1886-1924 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - ABCFM Year Book of Missions / Calendar of Prayer, 1925-1958 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - ABCFM Directory and Calendar of Prayer, 1959-1961 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - UCBWM Directory and Calendar of Prayer, 1961-1970 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report of the ABCFM: 97th, 101st, 102nd, 106th, 113th, 116th, 117th, 118th, 1907-1928 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Annual Report of the ABCFM: 119th-129th, 131st-142nd, 144th-146th, 148th-149th, 1929-1959 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report of the ABCFM: 150th; Annual Report of the UCBWM: 152nd-162nd, 1960-1972 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report and Calendar of Prayer of the UCBWM: 163rd -169th, 1973-1981 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report and Calendar of Prayer of the UCBWM: 170th -176th, 178th, 1980-1988 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Annual Report and Calendar of Prayer of the UCBWM: 177th, 179th, 1987-1989 (Box 198, Folder 16-17)
    - In Mission: A Calendar of Prayer for the United Church of Christ (UCBHM and UCBWM), 1990-1996 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Annual Reports UCBWM and UCB Home Ministries, 1990,1991, 1993 (Box 198, Folder 18-20)
    - Misc. UCBWM Annual Meeting material: Keynote Address by Alford Carleton, program of the 157th Annual Meeting; program of the 158th Annual Meeting, 1962, 1966, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - UCBWM Annual Meeting materials: Daily bulletin, attendance and personalities, business and reports, speeches, finances, miscellaneous, minutes, notes, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - UCBWM Annual Meeting materials: UCBWM Annual Meeting materials: Daily bulletin, attendance and personalities, business and reports, speeches, finances, miscellaneous, minutes, notes, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - UCBWM Annual Meeting materials: Daily bulletin, attendance and personalities, business and reports, speeches, finances, miscellaneous, minutes, notes, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 15-16)
    - UCBWM Annual Meeting materials: Daily bulletin, attendance and personalities, business and reports; speeches, finances, miscellaneous, minutes, notes (includes a vinyl recording), 1972 (Box 51, Folder 17-18)
    - UCBWM Annual Meeting materials: Daily bulletin, attendance and personalities, business and reports, speeches, finances, miscellaneous, minutes, notes, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Partners in Mission materials: Profiles of partners, PIM correspondence; World population year materials; Internationalizing the UCBWM, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - UCBWM Annual Meeting materials: Daily rap, attendance and personalities, business and reports; Programs and worship services, speeches, finances, miscellaneous, minutes, personal notes, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 21-22)
    - UCBWM Annual Meeting materials: incl. daily rap, attendance and personalities, business, reports, speeches, finances, preparartory material; recognition service bulletin; Alford Carleton's message; Salem, MA welcome materials; various reports on missions; newspaper clippings, notes, 1975-1977 (Box 53, Folder 23-28)
    - UCBWM Annual Meeting materials: Daily rap, attendance and personalities, business, reports, finance, worship services, speeches, 1978-1980 (Box 54, Folder 29-34)
    - UCBWM Annual Meeting materials: Attendance and personalities, preparatory reading, business, minutes, reports; committee correspondence, finances, miscellaneous, attendance and personalities, daily rap and information, worship service and speeches, 1981-1983 (Box 55, Folder 35-41)
    - UCBWM Annual Meeting materials: Missionary Herald and information, attendance and personalities, business; worship services, notes, speeches, finance, notes, 1984-1987 (Box 56, Folder 42-47)
    - UCBWM Annual Meeting materials: Missionary Herald, members, business, preparatory readings, reports, worship services and speeches, financial, UCC structure paper, staff bios, 1988-1992 (Box 57, Folder 48-53)
    - UCBWM Board of Directors Meeting materials: Agenda and attendance, minutes and ex cab actions, treasury reports, committee dockets, personnel (reappointments and terminations), 1970-1972 (Box 58, Folder 54-61)
    - UCBWM Board of Directors Meeting materials: Program, financial reports, board correspondence, committee reports and recs, north american interchurch study, notes, minutes, 1972-1975 (Box 59, Folder 62-70)
    - UCBWM Board of Directors Meeting materials: Minutes, notes, program, attendance, memos, regional reports, financial reports, agendas, committe reports and recs, "moratorium," "ecology," policies, etc., 1975-1977 (Box 60, Folder 71-77)
    - UCBWM Board of Directors Meeting materials: Program, attendance, roster, committee reports and recs, memos, agenda, news clippings, regional committee reports; memos, re: South Africa, etc., 1978-1980 (Box 61, Folder 78-86)
    - UCBWM Board of Directors Meeting materials: Minutes, program, committee reports and recs, correspondence, WCC, notes, financial reports, agendas; memos; re: immigration, resolution, haystack revival, infant formula, etc., 1980-1982 (Box 62, Folder 87-94)
    - UCBWM Board of Directors Meeting materials: Program; minutes; financial reports; attendance; committee reports and recs; re: Middle East, Central America, South Africa, missionary compensation, WCC, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 95-100)
    - UCBWM Board Updates (Corporate Briefings); UCBWM history highlights, 1974-1985 (Box 63, Folder 101-103)
  - Additional reports and documents
    - First Ten Reports of the ABCFM 1810-1820 (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Ad Hoc Committee to Plan for Planning, 1967 Sep (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Documents leading to Statement of Purpose, 1967 Sep (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Survey of UCC opinions and attitudes toward World Ministries, 1970 (Box 198, Folder 15)
- Resource Files: ABCFM/UCBWM Geographical / Topical Files, 1810-1990s; Series VI
  This series contains reports, brochures, pamphlets, writings, photographs and ephemera related to ABCFM/UCBWM missionaries, schools, hospitals and other mission activities. Many of the items are published on the mission field and provide valuable on-the-ground documentation. David and Virginia Stowe developed these resources as a sort of "vertical file" in the UCBWM New York office. Materials that were official archives or publications of the UCBWM have been sent to their archives in Cleveland. The documentation is particularly strong in the area of China because the Stowes served as missionaries there from 1947-1950 and developed many life-long relationships with missionary colleagues. These colleagues often sent Stowe materials related to their work.
  - Geographically arranged material
    - Africa
      - General
        - Canadian Board for Missions, 1916 (Box 64, Folder 1)
        - Churches and religious organizations, 1957-1974 (Box 64, Folder 2)
        - History; Newsletters, pamphlets, 1955-1989 (Box 64, Folder 3-4)
        - Photographs, 1956-1978, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 5-6)
        - Posters: The American Board in Africa, and others (Box 64, Folder 7)
        - Research files, 1960-1969 (Box 64, Folder 8)
        - Reuling, John: Oral history transcriptions, 1968,n.d. (Box 64, Folder 9)
        - ACC Bulletin; All Africa Conference of Churches, 1963 Oct (Box 176, Folder 1-2)
        - Literacy, 1968-1979 (Box 176, Folder 3-4)
        - Reports from trips of UCBWM administrators, 1962, 1971-1972 (Box 176, Folder 5)
        - Evangelical Presbyterian Church, 1955 (Box 176, Folder 6)
      - Angola
        - Samuel B. Coles: photographs, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 10)
        - American Board institutions, 1958-1959 (Box 65, Folder 11)
        - Chilesso Hospital, 1932-1958 (Box 65, Folder 12)
        - Church/ missions, incl. slides, 1928-1962 (Box 65, Folder 13-15)
        - Currie Institute, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 16)
        - Dondi Hospital, 1937-1956 (Box 65, Folder 17)
        - Galangue Hospital, 1937-1956 (Box 65, Folder 18)
        - Hospital and education slides (Box 65, Folder 19-22)
        - Historical documentation incl. re. Dondi: Historical, map, 1933-1985 (Box 65, Folder 23-26)
        - Mission history/ Jubilee, 1935-1996, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 27-32)
        - Newsbulletins, printed reports, 1917-1954 (Box 66, Folder 33-34)
        - Personnel: slides, pictures, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 35)
        - Research files, incl. report of Task Force XIII of The World Council of Churches, 1916-1990, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 36-40)
        - Slides, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 41-42)
        - Photos: Young child, group photos; Jose Chippinda (Box 67, Folder 43-44)
      - Azania (South Africa)
        - Liberation movements - newsletter of Pan Africanist Congress of Azania (South Africa): Azania News, 1973-1974 (Box 68, Folder 45)
      - Botswana
        - Research file, 1979, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 46)
      - Congo
        - Congo Protestant Relief Agency, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 47)
      - Gabon
        - Letters, 1849,1868 (Box 68, Folder 49)
      - Ghana
        - Evangelical Presbyterian Church, etc.: Newsletters, etc., 1957-1981 (Box 68, Folder 50)
        - Evangelical Presbyterian Church Worawora Hospital, 1962-1975 (Box 68, Folder 51)
        - Peki Theological Seminary, 1965, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 52)
        - History, missions, booklets, 1947-1999 (Box 68, Folder 53-55)
        - Photos: Evangelical Presbyterian Church; Trinity College, etc., 1970, 1975-1982 (Box 68, Folder 56-57)
      - Malawi
        - Report on the Churches and Social Develpment, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 58)
      - Mozambique
        - Spencer, Leon: "Toward an African Church in Mozambique", 1985 (Box 69, Folder 59)
        - Reports, letters, emails, 1967-1998 (Box 69, Folder 60-61)
      - Rhodesia
        See also Zimbabwe
        - Sithole, Ndabaningi: Autobiographical sketch, writings, correspondence, photographs, etc, 1954-1981, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 62-64)
        - Chikore School, 1950-1958 (Box 69, Folder 65)
        - Hospitals, 1944-1960 (Box 70, Folder 66)
        - Mount Silinda Institute, and photographs of Nurse Teddy Buck, 1934-1958 (Box 70, Folder 67)
        - Missions, 1940-1952, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 68-69)
        - Photographs, 1966-1977 (Box 70, Folder 70)
        - Lord, Charles Robert; "The Birth of a Mission"; Peters, Claude R.; "The Rhodesia Mission of the U.C.C., n.d. (Box 176, Folder 7-8)
      - South Africa
        - General
          - Dhliway, Selby: Honours Thesis, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 71)
          - Churches, 1960-1966 (Box 70, Folder 72)
          - Thesis: "Among the Bantu in Africa" by Fred Field Goodsell, 1962,1989 (Box 70, Folder 73)
          - Dictionary of South African Biography: Entries, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 74)
          - Various pamphlets, 1905-1996 (Box 70, Folder 75)
          - Photographs, 1979-1980 n.d. (Box 70, Folder 76)
          - Incl. Goodsell, Fred Field; Memorial from the Natal Native Mission Reserves; Bantu Congregational Church, 1935-1976 (Box 177, Folder 11-13)
        - Durban
          - Durban Museum, 1947,1994 (Box 68, Folder 48)
        - Inanda
          - Reuling, John and Eleanor, 1954-1959 (Box 71, Folder 77)
          - Wing, Rev. Joseph: Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 71, Folder 78)
          - Inanda Seminary, 1969-1984 (Box 71, Folder 79-82)
          - Inanda Seminary, 1961 (Box 177, Folder 14)
          - Photographs: Inanda Seminary, 1958-1977 (Box 71, Folder 83-84)
        - Johannesburg
          - Bridgeman Memorial Hospital, 1939-1953 (Box 72, Folder 85a)
        - Kuruman
          - Letters of Lawrence Gilley re. history of mission, 1998-1999 (Box 72, Folder 85b)
          - Pamphlets re. Kurumaan Moffat Mission, history of Setswana Bible, 1987-1998 (Box 72, Folder 85c)
        - Kwa Zulu
          - Buthelezi, Chief Gatsha, 1961-1979 (Box 72, Folder 86)
        - Natal
          - Champion, Allison (Mr.), 1913-1930 (Box 72, Folder 87)
          - Dube, John DD;Ph.D, 1953,n.d. (Box 72, Folder 88)
          - Emerson, Mabel E., 1944-1945 (Box 72, Folder 89)
          - Lindley, Lindsay (Box 72, Folder 90)
          - Luthuli, Albert John: Correspondence, newspaper clippings, articles, writings by Luthuli, 1948-1972 (Box 72, Folder 91-94)
          - Makanya, Constance and Tantsi, Ntombi (Makanya's cousin), 1946 (Box 72, Folder 95)
          - Adams College / Federal Theological Seminary, incl. photo, 1931-1984, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 96-98)
          - American Board missions, 1935-1959 (Box 73, Folder 99)
          - McCord Zulu Hospital, 1935-1959 n.d. (Box 73, Folder 100)
          - Missions financial records by Norman L. Rice, 1928-1934 1987 (Box 73, Folder 101)
          - School and church photographs, 1958 (Box 73, Folder 102)
        - Transvaal
          - Wigespruit Center, 1954-1961 (Box 73, Folder 103)
      - Tanzania
        - Christian Council of Tanzania, 1960s (Box 74, Folder 104)
      - Togo
        - Djaho, Doga, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 105)
        - Dokpo, Melle: scholar in France, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 106)
        - Missions, 1957-1984 (Box 74, Folder 107)
        - Photos of natives and missionaries, 1964-1981 (Box 74, Folder 108)
      - Zambia
        - Mindolo Ecumenical Foundation, 1970-1974 (Box 74, Folder 109)
        - Theological Education by Extension, 1984,n.d. (Box 74, Folder 110)
        - United Church, 1970-1980 (Box 74, Folder 111)
        - Research files, 1961-1973 (Box 74, Folder 112)
        - Photos of missionaries, etc., 1978 (Box 74, Folder 113)
      - Zimbabwe
        See also Rhodesia
        - History, 1940-1978 (Box 74, Folder 114-118)
        - Missions., missionaries, national leaders, 1939-1993 (Box 75, Folder 119-122)
        - Photos of missionaries and natives, 1959-1964 n.d. (Box 75, Folder 123)
        - Bates, Mary Kezia; "The Diary of Mary Kezia Bates", 1916-1927 (Box 176, Folder 9)
        - United Church of Christ, 1993 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Asia
      - General
        - Copland, Margaret: "Fun and Festivals from the Rim of East Asia", 1962 (Box 75, Folder 124)
      - Burma
        - Service ministry flyer, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 125)
      - Ceylon
        - Uduvil Girls' School, 1948-1952 (Box 75, Folder 126)
        - Union College (The American Board), 1949-1954 (Box 75, Folder 127)
        - National church leaders, slides, 1949-1970 (Box 75, Folder 128)
        - Research files, 1944-1991 (Box 76, Folder 129)
        - "Union Magazine", 1947,1954 (Box 76, Folder 130)
      - China
        - Individuals
          - Ballou, Earle H.: Correspondence, etc., 1959-1987 (Box 76, Folder 131)
          - Baumgarten, Fritz: Booklets, 1940-1947 (Box 76, Folder 132)
          - Bliss, Edward L.: Memorial writing, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 133)
          - Boynton, Grace M.; "The Missionary as Observer: Grace M. Boynton in China, 1919-1950", 1980 (Box 177, Folder 17)
          - Carleton, Alford: "The Silver Chalice of Canton" pamphlets, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 134)
          - Chandler, Helen Davis: Funeral program, 1982, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 135)
          - Cook, Alma: Correspondence, 1940 (Box 76, Folder 136)
          - Cross, Laura: Death notice, booklet of poems, correspondence, 1950-1970 (Box 76, Folder 137)
          - Dizney, Helen: Correspondence, writings, 1923-1982 (Box 76, Folder 138)
          - Galt, Edith: Death notices, writings, correspondence, 1936-1961 (Box 76, Folder 139)
          - Goddard, Dwight: "A Chapter in Chinese History", 1906 (Box 76, Folder 140)
          - Goodrich, Chauncey: Articles, writings, 1903-1925 (Box 76, Folder 141)
          - Hartwell, Emily:, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 142)
          - Hausske, Albert C.: Correspondence, articles, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 143)
          - Heininger, Alfred: Correspondence, 1946-1987 (Box 76, Folder 144)
          - Hemingway, Isabel: Correspondence, jobs listing, 1986, n.d. (Box 76, Folder 145)
          - Hemingway, Mary: Pamphlets, writings, 1908-1928 (Box 76, Folder 146)
          - Hibbard, Earl R.: "Across...Asia's Backdoor", 1967 (Box 76, Folder 147)
          - Horn, Josie: Photographs, correspondence, 1918-1946 (Box 76, Folder 148)
          - Huggins, Alice Margaret: Correspondence, etc., 1951-1962 (Box 76, Folder 149)
          - Hunter, James A.: Memorial service, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 150)
          - Lee, Olga: Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 77, Folder 151)
          - Leiper, Henry Smith: Memorial writing, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 152)
          - Lovatt, Ethel: Correspondence, 1941-1952 (Box 77, Folder 153)
          - Lum, Maryette: "Farmer's Song", n.d. (Box 77, Folder 154)
          - MacInnis, Don: Correspondence to Stowe; letters from China, 1947,1999 (Box 77, Folder 155)
          - Martin, W.: Letter, 1915 (Box 77, Folder 156)
          - Matthews, Harold: Writings, 1937-1968 (Box 77, Folder 157)
          - McCann, Robert Ezra, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 158)
          - Meng, Chin: Correspondence, 1937 (Box 77, Folder 159)
          - Mensendiek, William: Around the Forbidden Country, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 160)
          - Miner, Luella: Pamphlet, correspondence, 1920,1933 (Box 77, Folder 161)
          - Pettus, William Winston: Correspondence, 1941-1945 (Box 77, Folder 162)
          - Pollock, Pearl: Writings, 1942 (Box 77, Folder 163)
          - Porter, Rev. Lucius Chapin: Correspondence, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 164)
          - Reed, Alice: China Missionaries Oral History Project, 1944,1969 (Box 77, Folder 165)
          - Robinson, Olga: Pamphlets, 1926,1935 (Box 77, Folder 166)
          - Sattertwaite, David: Correspondence, 1947 (Box 77, Folder 167)
          - Shaw, Ernest (Mr. and Mrs.): Correspondence, 1950,1958 (Box 77, Folder 168)
          - Smith, Arthur: "Arthur Henderson Smith and the American Mission in China", 1987 (Box 77, Folder 169)
          - Strong, Robbins (Mr. and Mrs.): Pamphlet, 1943-1944 (Box 77, Folder 170)
          - Van Kirk, Ruth: Memorial writings, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 171)
          - Whitener, Sterling: Newspaper clippings, etc., 1996 (Box 77, Folder 172)
          - Whittley, W.W., 1971-1990 (Box 77, Folder 173)
          - Wilbur, Leonard Fisk: Memorial bulletin, 1940 (Box 77, Folder 174)
        - Institutions
          - American Board Missions in China, other missions, 1907-1979 (Box 78, Folder 175)
          - Bridgeman Academy, 1918-1936 (Box 78, Folder 176)
          - China's ABCFM: Photos and notes, 1915-1984 (Box 78, Folder 177)
          - Christian Rural Service Union, 1945-1950 (Box 78, Folder 178)
          - Churches, 1957-1980 (Box 78, Folder 179)
          - Church Addresses, 1980, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 180)
          - Evangelical Reform Church in China, 1988-1990 (Box 78, Folder 181)
          - Fenchow Station: North China Mission of the American Board, 1915-1941 (Box 78, Folder 182)
          - Hospitals, Medical work: Correspondence, photos,etc., 1929-1941 (Box 78, Folder 183)
          - Medical Relief Council, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 184)
          - North China College: Catalogue, 1898 (Box 78, Folder 185)
          - Reports of Council of the North China Kung Li Hui, 1941-1950 (Box 78, Folder 186)
          - Union Bible Training School for Women: Annual Reports, 1940-1950 (Box 78, Folder 187)
          - United Church of Christ, 1971-1982 (Box 78, Folder 188)
          - Yenching University: Guide, correspondence, reports, etc., 1929-1983 (Box 78, Folder 189)
        - Topical
          - ABCFM in China: History, 1912-1985 (Box 79, Folder 190)
          - China social issues, 1986-1988 (Box 79, Folder 191)
          - College students protests: Newspaper articles, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 192)
          - Communism, 1961-1983 (Box 79, Folder 193)
          - Conference reports, 1912-1987 (Box 79, Folder 194)
          - Foochow: History, 1938-1957 (Box 79, Folder 195)
          - Images of China and art, 1961, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 196)
          - Manchuria: Pamphlets, etc., 1932-1958 (Box 79, Folder 197)
          - Missions History in China, 1977-1988 (Box 79, Folder 198)
          - "The Mission Mirror" newsletter, 1936,1939 (Box 80, Folder 199)
          - North China Missionaries, 1920-1935 (Box 80, Folder 200)
          - Records and reports, 1938-1970 (Box 80, Folder 201)
          - Reports from vistors to China, 1979-1985 (Box 80, Folder 202)
          - Research: Christian missions, 1950-1972 (Box 80, Folder 203)
          - Pamphlets, books, maps, 1935-1972 (Box 177, Folder 15-16)
        - Photographs
          - American Board former hospital in Beijing, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 204)
          - North China Mission, 1873 (Box 80, Folder 205)
          - Peiping "The Temple of Heaven", ca.1940s (Box 80, Folder 206)
      - Hong Kong
        - Christian Institutions, 1951-1968 (Box 80, Folder 207)
        - Evangelical and Reformed Church, 1954-1956 n.d. (Box 80, Folder 208)
        - Correspondence, votes, 1962-1971 (Box 80, Folder 209)
        - Council on Ecumenical Research, 1950s (Box 80, Folder 210)
        - Research files, 1963-1969 (Box 80, Folder 211-212)
      - India
        - Individuals